Guide to the Ladies of Llangollen Collection, 1774-1991 RL.11554
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Objects, 3
  - Cup or mug without handle, green and white with relief images of "Ladies of Langollen" on one side and "Welsh Costumes" on the other; chip at rim, 10cm x 10cm x 8.5cm (Box 7)